Jacques Seligmann & Co.
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Exhibition Files, 1925-1977, undated, Series 4:; (Boxes 260-272; 5.5 linear feet)
  - Exhibits, 1925-1977, undated, 4.1:
    - 1936: Exhibition of Sculptures of Old African Civilizations, 1936, undated (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - 1937: Twenty Years in the Evolution of Picasso, 1903-1923, 1937 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - 1937: Courbet to Seurat, 1937 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - 1937: Chefs d'Ouevre de L'Art Français (Paris), 1937 (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - 1937: Indian Textiles from the Collection of H. H. The Maharani of Baroda, 1935-1939 (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - 1937: Vincent van Gogh Exhibition (Paris), 1937 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - 1938: Edgar Degas Exhibition (see also Newpaper Clippings in 4.2: Miscellaneous Files), 1938, undated (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - 1938: Juan Gris, 1887-1927, 1938 (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - 1938: Portraits by Sir Henry Raeburn, 1756-1823, 1938 (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - 1938: Sculpture Exhibition by Electra Waggoner, 1938 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - 1938: Charles Shannon: Paintings of the South, 1938 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - 1939: Recent Paintings by Gallatin, Morris, and Shaw, 1938-1939 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - 1939: The Stage (Box 261)
      - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 261, Folder 15)
      - Catalog and Related Material, 1939, undated (Box 261, Folder 16)
      - Lists, 1939 (Box 261, Folder 17)
      - Miscellany, 1939, undated (Box 261, Folder 18)
    - 1939: Public Education Association Exhibition, (canceled exhibition that was replaced by The Stage, 1939), 1939 (Box 261, Folder 19)
    - 1940: New York World's Fair (Box 262)
      - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1940 January-March (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1940 March (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1940 April (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1940 May-December (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Daily Attendance Roster, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 6)
      - Financial Budget, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 7)
      - Lecture Notes by John H. B. Knowlton, undated (Box 262, Folder 8)
      - Lecture Notes by Helen Ederheimer, undated (Box 262, Folder 9)
      - List of Board of Directors, Rules, and Regulations, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 10)
      - List of Pictures for Masterpieces of Art, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 11)
      - Photograph, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 12)
      - Printed Material, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 13)
      - Sales Report, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - 1941: Christmas Exhibition, 1941, undated (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - 1943: Gift Box, Christmas Exhibition, undated (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - 1944: Fernand Léger: Les Plongeurs, 1944 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - 1946: 1910-1912: The Climactic Years in Cubism, 1946, undated, (2 folders) (Box 263, Folder 4-5)
    - 1946: Prints, Christmas Exhibition, 1946 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - 1947: The Printmakers, Founders Exhibition, 1947 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - 1947: Roger de La Fresnaye, 1885-1925: Watercolors-Gouaches-Drawings, 1947 (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - 1947: The Sea, 1947 (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - 1948: Vuillard, 1865-1940: His Dynamic Early Period (Box 263)
      - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 263, Folder 10)
      - Catalog Text, Proofs, and Lists, 1948 (Box 263, Folder 11)
      - Reviews and Publicity, 1948 (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - 1950: Nine Paintings by Rico Lebrun, 1900-, 1950 (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - 1951: Master Drawings of Five Centuries, 1951 (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - 1951-1952: Odilon Redon, 1840-1916: Pastels and Drawings (Box 264)
      - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 264, Folder 1)
      - Lists, 1951 (Box 264, Folder 2)
      - Material for Catalog, 1951-1952, undated (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1951 (Box 264, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - 1952: Illuminated Manuscripts, 11th Centuries to the 16th Centuries, from the Bibliothèque of Their Highnesses, the Dukes d'Arenberg (Box 264)
      - Bills for Catalog, 1951-1952 (Box 264, Folder 6)
      - Catalog, 1952 (Box 264, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 264, Folder 8)
      - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, 1952, undated (Box 264, Folder 9)
      - Labels, 1952, (not scanned) (Box 264, Folder 10)
      - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity, 1952 (Box 264, Folder 11)
      - Photographs, circa 1952 (Box 264, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases, circa 1952 (Box 264, Folder 13)
    - 1953: Master Drawings: European Drawings of Four Centuries, 1953 (Box 264, Folder 14)
    - 1953: Seventeenth Century French Paintings and Drawings (Box 265)
      - Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 265, Folder 1)
      - Exhibit Text, 1953 (Box 265, Folder 2)
      - List, Miscellaneous, 1953, undated (Box 265, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - Reviews, 1952-1953 (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - 1955: Engravings from the Celebrated Collection of the Dukes d'Arenberg (Box 265)
      - Catalog and Related Material, 1955 (Box 265, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 265, Folder 7)
      - Notes, circa 1953-1955 (Box 265, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, 1955 (Box 265, Folder 9)
      - Publicity and Reviews, 1955, undated (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - 1955-1956: Baron Antoine-Jean Gros: Painter of Battles - The First Romantic Painter, 1951-1956 (Box 265)
      - Catalogs and Related Material, 1955-1956 (Box 265, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 265, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 265, Folder 13)
      - Notifications of Complimentary Catalogs, and Thank You Notes, 1956-1959 (Box 265, Folder 14)
      - Photographs, circa 1955-1956 (Box 265, Folder 15)
    - 1955-1956: Baron Antoine-Jean Gros: Painter of Battles - The First Romantic Painter, 1951-1956 (Box 266)
      - Reviews, 1955-1956, (2 folders) (Box 266, Folder 1-2)
    - 1957 (November 18-December 7): Master Drawings, 1957 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - 1957: Religious Art of the Earlier Centuries, 1957 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - 1957: 17th Century Internationalism, United Nations Exhibition, 1957, undated (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - 1958: French Drawings from American Collections: Clouet to Matisse, 1958-1959 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - 1959 (November 16-December 5): Master Drawings, 1959 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - 1960 (November 7-28): Master Drawings, 1960 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - 1961 (October 23-November 11): Master Drawings, 1961 (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - 1961: Three Sculptors, 1961 (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - 1962 (November 5-24): Master Drawings, 1962-1963 (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - 1964 November 4-25: Master Drawings, 1964 (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - 1965 October 23-November 13: Master Drawings, 1965 (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - 1966 November 16-December 10: Master Drawings, 1966 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - 1967 November 4-25: Master Drawings, 1967 (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - 1967-1968: Young Newcomers and Newcomers '68, 1967-1968, undated (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - 1968 November 2-23: Master Drawings, 1968 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - 1969 November 15-December 6: Master Drawings, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - 1970 October 31-November 21: Master Drawings, 1970 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - 1971: Contemporary American Watercolors and Drawings, 1970-1971, undated (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - 1971: Four Newcomers, 1971, undated (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - 1971: Master Drawings, 1971 November 6-December 4 (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - 1972 November 4-25: Master Drawings, 1972 (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - 1972: New Talent, 1972, undated (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - 1972: Paintings by Grevis Melville and Ceramics by Emily Rose, 1971-1972 (Box 267, Folder 12)
    - 1973 November 17-December 8: Master Drawings, 1973 (Box 267, Folder 13)
    - 1973: One by Each, 1969-1973 (Box 267, Folder 14)
    - 1974: Newcomers 74, 1974 (Box 267, Folder 15)
    - 1977: Newcomers 77, 1977 (Box 267, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Files, 1935-1972, undated, 4.2:
    This subseries includes correspondence with clients and museums concerning loans, shipping, and administrative matters, and clippings about exhibitions held. Also found are lists of clients to whom exhibition catalogs were sent and a chronology of exhibitions held at the New York and Paris galleries.
    Arrangement is by subject heading and, thereafter, chronological.
    This series has been scanned in entirety with the exception of a folder listing clients to whom exhibition catalogs were sent.
    - Competitions and Annual Shows, 1947 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Regarding Giotto Exhibition in Florence, Italy, 1937 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Catalogs Sent, 1946-1947, undated, (not scanned) (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1952-1956 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1957-1959 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1960 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1961-1962 (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1963 (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1964 (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1965 (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition Loans, 1966-1971 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Lists of Exhibitions Held, undated (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Announcements, circa 1920s (Box 268, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1923-1929 (Box 268, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1935, 1949, undated (Box 268, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbooks, 1925-1970, undated, 4.3:
    In this subseries are exhibit text, brochures, printed material, and clippings originally housed in large scrapbooks that documented exhibitions held by Jacques Seligmann & Co., Inc.
    This bulk of this series has been scanned. Some news clippings have not been scanned and only the covers of some exhibition catalogs have been scanned.
    - Scrapbook no. 1, Allegory of Peace, undated (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook no. 2, 1947-1970 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook no. 3, Portraits par Ingres et ses Eleves, 1934, (3 folders) (Box 271, Folder 1-3)
    - Scrapbook no. 4, 1925-1942 (Box 272, Folder 1)
- Reference Files, circa 1904-circa 1977, Series 5:; (Boxes 273-278; 2.25 linear feet)
  Jacques Seligmann & Co., Inc., continuously purchased and retained books, articles, and exhibition and sale catalogs for reference use at its galleries. This series consists of Gallery Library Card Catalogs and a Photograph Reference Index for works of art.
  Entries for the card catalog were assigned numbers. The library holdings largely consisted of exhibition catalogs, art history and criticism titles, and biographies and monographs on individual artists.
  The Photograph Reference Index consists of handwritten and typed records on works of art that generally include date of photograph, stock number, artist, size of work, and publications in which a photograph of the artwork has appeared. Of special interest to researchers will be the notations made on two entries listed under the name, Seligman, G. S., identifying those works of art as looted by the German forces during the occupation of Paris.
  The series is organized into two subseries:
  5.1: Gallery Library Card Catalogs, circa 1904-circa 1977
  5.2: Photograph Reference Index, circa 1904-circa 1960
  Series 5.1. has been scanned; series 5.2. has not been scanned.
  - Gallery Library Card Catalogs, circa 1904-circa 1977, 5.1:
    At the beginning of the Card Catalog I are four index cards that explain the firm's filing system: books were generally filed under subject and author; exhibitions were filed by country, city, gallery, museum, or subject; private collections were filed under "Collections"; exhibition catalogs of individual collections were filed under the collector's name; auction sales were sometimes listed by subject; the category "Dictionaries" gave listings of general reference works; and "General" listings were books that did not fit other classifications. In Card Catalog II many of the entries reference exhibition or auction catalogs.
    - Card Catalog I, circa 1904-circa 1971, 5.1.1:
      The arrangement of this subseries is alphabetical. This series has not been scanned.
      - A-O, (not scanned) (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - P-Z, (not scanned) (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Card Catalog II, circa 1925-circa 1977, 5.1.2:
      The arrangement of this subseries is alphabetical. Interspersed within the larger alphabetical arrangement are small, specialized subject headings. This series has not been scanned.
      - A-F, (not scanned) (Box 275, Folder 1)
      - G-O, (not scanned) (Box 276, Folder 1)
      - P-Z, (not scanned) (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Reference Index, circa 1904-circa 1960, 5.2:
    Within the card file are three series of indexes. Arrangement of the first is by medium; the second series is arranged alphabetically by name of collector or collection; and the third lists painters, arranged alphabetically, followed by sculptors. Note that there may not be index cards for every letter of the alphabet referenced in the container listing. This series has been scanned in entirety.
    - Index by Medium (Box 278)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 1)
      - Armour, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 2)
      - Ceramics, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 3)
      - Drawings, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 4)
      - Enamels, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 5)
      - Furniture, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 6)
      - Ivory, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 7)
      - Jewelry, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 8)
      - Manuscripts, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 9)
      - Paintings, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 10)
      - Sculpture, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 11)
      - Tapestries, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Index by Collector/Collections (Box 278)
      - A, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 13)
      - B, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 14)
      - C, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 15)
      - D, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 16)
      - E-F, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 17)
      - G, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 18)
      - H-I-J, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 19)
      - K, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 20)
      - L, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 21)
      - M, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 22)
      - N, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 23)
      - O-P, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 24)
      - Q-R, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 25)
      - S, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 26)
      - T, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 27)
      - U-V, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 28)
      - W, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 29)
      - X-Y-Z, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 30)
    - Index by Artist, Painters (Box 278)
      - A-B, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 31)
      - C, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 32)
      - D, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 33)
      - E-F, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 34)
      - G, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 35)
      - H-I-J, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 36)
      - K-L, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 37)
      - M-N-O, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 38)
      - P-Q, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 39)
      - R, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 40)
      - S, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 41)
      - T-U-V, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 42)
      - W-X-Y-Z, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 43)
    - Index by Artist, Sculptors (Box 278)
      - A-B, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 44)
      - C, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 45)
      - D-E-F, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 46)
      - G-H, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 47)
      - I-J-K-L, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 48)
      - M-N-O, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 49)
      - P-Q, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 50)
      - R-S, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 51)
      - T-U-V, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 52)
      - W-X-Y-Z, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous Numbered Cards, circa 1904-circa 1960 (Box 278, Folder 54)
- Inventory and Stock Files, 1923-1971, undated, Series 6:; (Boxes 279-289; 4.5 linear feet)
  This series includes bound and loose stock and inventory catalogs and lists prepared by the New York and Paris offices. Inventory catalogs are arranged by location, inventory number, genre, and ownership for stock in New York and Paris. Although many of the catalogs are complete and in numbered order, others appear to be missing inventory numbers. It was quite common for the firm to remove part of an inventory catalog when an item had been sold and file the sheet in other files in the firm's records. Some of the inventory number sequences overlap due to copies of listings being filed in more than one place. Also found are miscellaneous inventory lists as well as an inventory of the firms photographic negative file of works of art.
  This series is organized into four subseries:
  6.1: Stock Catalogs, New York Office, 1923-1971, undated
  6.2: Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs, New York Office, 1920-1973
  6.3: Stock Catalogs, Paris Office, 1924-1939
  6.4: Negative Files, undated
  This series has been scanned in entirety, with the exception of 6.4: Negative files.
  - Stock Catalogs, New York Office, 1923-1971, undated, 6.1:
    - Inventory nos. 1-108 and 423-695, circa pre-1923 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Inventory nos. 700-901, circa pre-1923 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Inventory nos. 902-1200, circa pre-1923 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Inventory nos. 1206-1884, circa pre-1923 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Incomplete Inventory, 1923 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Inventory nos. 1-1324, 1924 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Inventory nos. 1325-2689, 1924 (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - Inventory nos. 2010-2380, 1924-1925 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Inventory nos. 2381-2923, 1924-1925 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Inventory nos. 2924-2999 and Index, 1924-1925 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Inventory nos. 2096-3200, 1925-1926 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Inventory nos. 3201-3414 and Index, 1925-1926 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Inventory nos. 2000-3299, 1926-1927 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Inventory nos. 3303-3752 and Index, 1926-1927 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Inventory nos. 2003-3799, 1927-1928 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Inventory nos. 3782-4080 and Index, 1927-1928 (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Inventory nos. 2007-3984, 1928-1929 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - Inventory nos. 4005-4501 and Index, 1928-1929 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - Inventory nos. 2007-3984, 1929-1930 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Inventory nos. 3985-4281 and Index, 1929-1930 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Inventory by Artist, 1930s, undated (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Inventory nos. 2007-4666, 1930-1931 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Inventory nos. 4670-5043 and Index, 1930-1931 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Inventory nos. 2007-5071, 1931-1932 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Inventory nos. 5073-5264 and Index, 1931-1932 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - Inventory nos. 2007-4938, 1933-1934 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - Inventory nos. 4945-5500 and Index, 1933-1934 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Inventory nos. 2284-6156 and Index, 1934-1935 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Inventory of Modern Works of Art by Genre and Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - Stock Catalog, 1935-1936 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Stock Catalog, 1936-1937 (Box 281, Folder 13)
    - Stock Catalog, 1937-1938 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Stock Catalog, 1938-1939, (2 folders) (Box 282, Folder 2-3)
    - Stock Catalog, 1940-1941, (2 folders) (Box 282, Folder 4-5)
    - Stock Catalog, 1942-1943 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Stock Catalog, 1944-1945 (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - Works of Art Sold or Taken out of Stock, 1946-1948 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Stock Catalog, 1950-1954, (4 folders) (Box 283, Folder 1-4)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 4453-8220, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1956-1971 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 8221-8425, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1956-1971 (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 8426-8629, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1956-1971, (2 folders) (Box 283, Folder 7-8)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 8632-8701, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1956-1971 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 8702-8787, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1956-1971 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 8788-8852, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1956-1971 (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 8863-8959, Paintings and Drawings, circa 1956-1971 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Stock Catalog, Inventory nos. 4786-8656, Sculpture, circa 1956-1971 (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Stock Catalog, undated (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Paintings and Pastels no. 1, 1927-1929 (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Paintings and Pastels no. 2, 1927-1931 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Engravings and Sculpture, 1926-1930 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Watercolors and Drawings no. 1, 1926-1928 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Watercolors and Drawings no. 2, 1926-1932 (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Watercolors and Drawings, undated (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Decorative Art, 1926-1931 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - Bound Stock Catalog: Objects of Decorative Art, undated (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - Bound Stock Lists: All Stock, 1926-1949 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Bound Stock Lists: All Stock, 1950-1960s (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs, New York Office, 1920-1973, 6.2:
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs, 1931, undated (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs: Jacques Seligmann & Co., Inc., Germain Seligman-Modern Paintings, Inc., circa 1930, undated (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs: Modern Paintings, Inc.; de Hauke & Co., Inc., 1930-1932 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs: Miscellaneous Descriptions, circa 1950-1954 (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs: Furniture Index, undated (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs: Picture Index, undated (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs: List and Photographs, vol. 1, 1920-1973 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Lists and Catalogs: List and Photographs, vol. 2, 1920-1973 (Box 287, Folder 8)
  - Stock Catalogs, Paris Office, 1924-1939, 6.3:
    - Stock Catalogs, circa 1924-1930, (2 folders) (Box 287, Folder 9-10)
    - Stock Catalogs, circa 1924-1930, (7 folders) (Box 288, Folder 1-7)
    - Stock Catalogs, 1935, (3 folders) (Box 288, Folder 8-10)
    - Objects on Consignment, 1939 (Box 288, Folder 11)
  - Negative Files, undated, 6.4:
    This series has not been scanned.
    - Negative Files, A-B, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Negative Files, C-D, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Negative Files, E-H, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Negative Files, I-L, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Negative Files, M-N, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Negative Files, O-P, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Negative Files, Q-R, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Negative Files, S-T, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Negative Files, U-Z, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Negative Files, Works of Art I, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Negative Files, Works of Art II, (not scanned) (Box 289, Folder 11)
- Financial Files and Shipping Records, 1910-1977, Series 7:; (Boxes 290-357; 30.5 linear feet)